pixelstores.com 2007-03-09

# osCommerce

The website you are visiting is fully owned by Summit Technology Group (furthermore described as STG) and is an extenstion of their support department. The privacy policy for this website and all of our websites is listed below.

**What if I do not feel comfortable about giving out my personal information?**

Please call our customer care center at 877-388-3779 toll free weekdays 10am to 7pm and Saturdays 10am to 4pm EST. They will ask for the same information however if you do not provide personal information, the staff will still try to assist you by phone without having a personal customer  
history with us.

**Privacy Policy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. STG recognizes your right to confidentiality and has a firm commitment to ensuring your privacy. This recognition guides every decision we make about how, where, and when to collect information. The personal information we do collect allows us to provide you with an exemplary shopping and ordering experience. The information you share with us is kept strictly confidential and fully secure. STG will never sell,distribute, or otherwise misuse this information. If you have any questions or concerns about this statement, or about the way your information is collected and used, please contact our management.

**Our Privacy Guarantee**  
STG is the sole collector and owner of our customers personally identifiable information. We do not sell, rent, or loan any of this information to any third party and we will not release it to any third party unless legally required to do so.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Website, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of information by STG and to the terms of this privacy policy. If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If we were to make a material change to our privacy policy, we will either post a notice on our Web site or send you an e-mail.

Polaroid, the Polaroid logo trademarks, and the Polaroid trade dress are owned by Polaroid Corporation and are used on these products under license from Polaroid. Polaroid does not manufacture this prouct or provide product warranty or support, which is provided by Flextronics NA in most countries. 

Summit Technology Group is an operational subsidary of Flextronics.
